let easydivisionquestions = [
    {
        question: "What is 18 ÷ 3",
        AnswerA: "4",
        AnswerB: "6",
        AnswerC: "7",
        AnswerD: "8",
        correctAnswer: "6",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 18 ÷ 6",
        AnswerA: "2",
        AnswerB: "3",
        AnswerC: "5",
        AnswerD: "6",
        correctAnswer: "3",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 14 ÷ 2",
        AnswerA: "5",
        AnswerB: "6",
        AnswerC: "7",
        AnswerD: "8",
        correctAnswer: "7",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 12 ÷ 3",
        AnswerA: "2",
        AnswerB: "3",
        AnswerC: "4",
        AnswerD: "6",
        correctAnswer: "4",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 48 ÷ 4",
        AnswerA: "12",
        AnswerB: "13",
        AnswerC: "14",
        AnswerD: "15",
        correctAnswer: "12",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 44 ÷ 4",
        AnswerA: "11",
        AnswerB: "13",
        AnswerC: "15",
        AnswerD: "17",
        correctAnswer: "11",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 39 ÷ 3",
        AnswerA: "11",
        AnswerB: "12",
        AnswerC: "13",
        AnswerD: "15",
        correctAnswer: "13",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 24 ÷ 8",
        AnswerA: "3",
        AnswerB: "5",
        AnswerC: "7",
        AnswerD: "8",
        correctAnswer: "3",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 32 ÷ 8",
        AnswerA: "2",
        AnswerB: "4",
        AnswerC: "6",
        AnswerD: "8",
        correctAnswer: "4",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 28 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "3",
        AnswerB: "4",
        AnswerC: "6",
        AnswerD: "8",
        correctAnswer: "4",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 49 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "3",
        AnswerB: "5",
        AnswerC: "7",
        AnswerD: "9",
        correctAnswer: "7",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 45 ÷ 15",
        AnswerA: "2",
        AnswerB: "3",
        AnswerC: "6",
        AnswerD: "9",
        correctAnswer: "3",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 48 ÷ 6",
        AnswerA: "6",
        AnswerB: "7",
        AnswerC: "8",
        AnswerD: "9",
        correctAnswer: "8",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 32 ÷ 16",
        AnswerA: "2",
        AnswerB: "3",
        AnswerC: "4",
        AnswerD: "6",
        correctAnswer: "2",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 22 ÷ 11",
        AnswerA: "2",
        AnswerB: "4",
        AnswerC: "8",
        AnswerD: "10",
        correctAnswer: "2",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 42 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "4",
        AnswerB: "6",
        AnswerC: "7",
        AnswerD: "8",
        correctAnswer: "6",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 64 ÷ 8",
        AnswerA: "5",
        AnswerB: "6",
        AnswerC: "7",
        AnswerD: "8",
        correctAnswer: "8",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 72 ÷ 9",
        AnswerA: "6",
        AnswerB: "7",
        AnswerC: "8",
        AnswerD: "9",
        correctAnswer: "8",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 90 ÷ 10",
        AnswerA: "8",
        AnswerB: "9",
        AnswerC: "10",
        AnswerD: "11",
        correctAnswer: "9",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 80 ÷ 10",
        AnswerA: "7",
        AnswerB: "8",
        AnswerC: "9",
        AnswerD: "10",
        correctAnswer: "8",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 50 ÷ 5",
        AnswerA: "10",
        AnswerB: "11",
        AnswerC: "13",
        AnswerD: "15",
        correctAnswer: "10",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 81 ÷ 9",
        AnswerA: "8",
        AnswerB: "9",
        AnswerC: "10",
        AnswerD: "11",
        correctAnswer: "9",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 100 ÷ 10",
        AnswerA: "5",
        AnswerB: "10",
        AnswerC: "15",
        AnswerD: "20",
        correctAnswer: "10",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 88 ÷ 8",
        AnswerA: "11",
        AnswerB: "12",
        AnswerC: "13",
        AnswerD: "14",
        correctAnswer: "11",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 63 ÷ 9",
        AnswerA: "5",
        AnswerB: "6",
        AnswerC: "7",
        AnswerD: "8",
        correctAnswer: "7",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 70 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "8",
        AnswerB: "9",
        AnswerC: "10",
        AnswerD: "11",
        correctAnswer: "10",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 54 ÷ 6",
        AnswerA: "6",
        AnswerB: "7",
        AnswerC: "8",
        AnswerD: "9",
        correctAnswer: "9",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 25 ÷ 5",
        AnswerA: "3",
        AnswerB: "4",
        AnswerC: "5",
        AnswerD: "6",
        correctAnswer: "5",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 50 ÷ 5",
        AnswerA: "5",
        AnswerB: "10",
        AnswerC: "15",
        AnswerD: "20",
        correctAnswer: "10",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 96 ÷ 8",
        AnswerA: "8",
        AnswerB: "9",
        AnswerC: "11",
        AnswerD: "12",
        correctAnswer: "12",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 35 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "3",
        AnswerB: "4",
        AnswerC: "5",
        AnswerD: "6",
        correctAnswer: "5",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 27 ÷ 9",
        AnswerA: "3",
        AnswerB: "5",
        AnswerC: "7",
        AnswerD: "9",
        correctAnswer: "3",
    },
]